(Leonard:)Uh-oh.
(Penny:)What?
(Leonard:)We got an email from the East Rutherford,
New Jersey, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual...
(Leonard:)...and Transgender Alliance.
They want another 1000 Penny Blossoms.
- Really?
- One-day rush.
I really need to take that off the website.
Okay, well, guess we better get started.
(Howard:)You can't be serious.
But, come on. What about
the living organism of the work force...
...and the American spirit?
(Penny:)And Jiminy Crockett at the Alamo?
(Sheldon:)Davy Crockett.
Jiminy Crockett was a cricket.
(Penny:)Yes, I know that, okay? I'm tired
and I've had 18 cups of coffee.
(Penny:)The point is, if we all just pull together,
we can do this. Who's with me?
(Howard:)Penny, although you may find it hard
to believe, we do have lives.